好吧，今天我想谈谈更多关于容错和
all right today I want to talk about bit
more about fault tolerance and
复制，然后查看有关vmware ft的今天论文的详细信息
replication and then look into the
details of today's paper about vmware ft
主题仍然具有容错能力，可以为您提供高可用性
the topics still fault tolerance to
provide high availability that is you
想要建立一个即使您知道某些计算机崩溃的硬件的服务器也是
want to build a server that even if some
hardware you know computer crashes is
参与服务，我们仍然愿意提供服务，并在一定程度上
involved in the service we still like to
provide the service and to the extent we
如果出现网络问题，并且我们还可以提供服务吗？
can we'd like to provide our service
also if there's network problems and the
我们在课程的这一部分中最少使用它的复制工具，因此
tool we're using its replication least
for this part of the course so it's
值得一问的是，复制有望解决什么样的故障
worth asking what kind of failures
replication can be expected to deal with
因为这不是一切
because it's not everything by any means
所以也许是最简单的表征我们正在谈论的失败类型的方法
so maybe the easiest way to characterize
the kind of failures we're talking about
是单台计算机的故障停止故障，我的意思是故障停止
is fail stop failures of a single
computer and what I mean by fail stop
这是一个通用术语，容错能力是
it's a sort of generic term and fault
tolerance is that if something goes
错误会说计算机只是停止执行它而已
wrong would say the computer the
computer simply stops executing it just
如果出现任何问题（特别是计算错误），则会停止
stops if anything goes wrong and in
particular it doesn't compute incorrect
结果，因此如果有人将电源线从服务器中踢出，那可能是
results so if somebody kicks the power
cable out of your server that's probably
如果他们拔下服务器，也会类似地产生故障停止失败
gonna generate a fail stop failure
similarly if they unplug your servers
网络连接，即使服务器仍在运行，所以这是一个
network connection even though the
server is still running so this is a
有点可笑，你知道完全被网络切断了，所以看着我
little bit funny you know be totally cut
off from the network so it looks at me
像外面一样停止了，所以我们可以处理的正是这些失败
outside like it just stopped so it's
really these failures we can deal with
复制还可以解决一些硬件问题，例如您知道
with replication this also covers some
hardware problems like you know maybe if
您服务器上的风扇坏了，因为您知道它要花50美分，也许
the fan on your server breaks because it
you know it cost 50 cents maybe that'll
导致CPU过热，CPU会干净地自行关闭，
cause the CPU to overheat and the CPU
will shut itself down cleanly and just
停止执行
stop executing
我们正在讨论的复制系统类型没有涵盖的内容
what's not covered by the kind of
replication systems we're talking about
是诸如错误，软件或硬件设计缺陷之类的东西
is things like bugs and software or
design defects in hardware so basically
不是错误，因为如果我们提供一些服务，您就会知道您是MapReduce的主人
not bugs because if we take some service
you know say you're a MapReduce master
例如，您知道我们复制并在两台计算机上运行它，
for example you know we replicated and
run it on two computers you know if
您的MapReduce母版或我的MapReduce母版中有一个错误
there's a bug in your MapReduce master
or my MapReduce master let's say
复制不会帮助我们，我们将计算出同样的错误
replications not going to help us we're
going to compute the same incorrect
我们的两个MapReduce主副本的结果
result on both of our copies of our
MapReduce master and everything looked
好的，他们会同意您恰好是错误的答案，所以我们不能依靠
fine they'll agree you just happen to be
the wrong answer so we can't depending
防止复制软件中的错误，我们无法针对
against bugs in the replicated software
and we can't defend against bugs in the
我们用来管理复制的任何方案，与我类似
whatever scheme we're using to manage
the replication and similarly as I
之前提到过，我们不能期望处理硬件中的错误
mentioned before we can't expect to deal
with bugs in the hardware the hardware
它计算错误，这至少对我们而言就是这样
it computes incorrectly that's just
that's the end for us at least with this
一种技术，尽管您知道肯定有硬件和
kind of technique although you know that
said there are definitely hardware and
如果幸运的话，该复制可能会导致的软件错误
software bugs that that replication
might if you're lucky might be able to
应对它，以便服务器中运行一些不相关的软件，并且
cope it so if there's some unrelated
software running in your server and it
导致服务器崩溃，也许是因为您的内核崩溃并重新启动，或者
causes the server to crash maybe because
your kernel to panic and reboot or
与您无关的事情与您所提供的服务有关
something it has nothing to do with you
know with your with the service you're
复制我们为您服务的那种失败很可能是
replicating then that kind of failure
for us for your service will may well be
失败停止，您知道内核将崩溃并且
fail stop
you know the kernel will panic and the
备份副本将类似地接管某些硬件错误
backup replicas will take over similarly
some kinds of hardware errors can be
变成了失败停止错误，例如，如果您通过网络发送数据包
turned into fail stop errors for example
if you send a packet over the network
而网络破坏了它，只是翻转了您的数据包中的一点，几乎
and the network corrupts it just flips a
bit in your packet that will almost
肯定会被磁盘块的数据包的校验和所捕获
certainly be caught by the checksum on
the packet same thing for a disk block
如果您将一些数据写入磁盘，并在一个月后将其退回，您可能知道
if you write some data to disk and weand
it back a month later you know maybe the
磁性表面并不完美，您知道最好的几个钻头之一是
magnetic surface isn't perfect and you
know one of the best couple of bits were
块中的错误，因为它是正确的，实际上是纠错
wrong in the block as it's right back
it's actually error correcting
在一定程度上可以修复磁盘块中的错误
that up to a certain point will fix
errors in disk blocks that you'll be
将您知道的随机硬件错误转化为纠正错误（如果您正在
turning you know random hardware errors
into as either correcting them if you're
超级幸运或至少检测到它们并将随机损坏转变为
super lucky or at least detecting them
and turning random corruption into a
检测到您知道该软件的故障，然后知道该故障
detected fault which you know the
software then knows that something that
错误，可以通过停止执行或采取一些措施将其转变为故障停止错误
wrong and can turn it into a fail stop
fault by stopping executing or take some
其他补救措施，但总的来说，我们真的只能期望处理失败
other remedial action but in general we
really can only expect to handle fail
停止故障还有复制的其他限制，您知道故障
stop faults there's other limits to
replication to you know the the failures
如果我们在两个副本的后面有一个主对象
in the if we have a primary in the back
of our two replicas or whatever we're
真的假设两者中的失败是独立的权利
really assuming that failures in the two
are independent right if there tend to
关联了故障，那么复制不会对我们有帮助
have correlated failures then
replication is not going to help us so
例如，如果我们的服装很大，我们购买了成千上万的计算机批次
for example if we're a big outfit and we
buy thousands of computers batches of
数以千计的计算机来自同一制造商的相同计算机，以及
thousands of computers identical
computers from the same manufacturer and
我们运行，您知道我们的副本位于同一购买的所有计算机上
we run you know our replicas is on all
on those computers we bought at the same
从同一个地方来的时间有点冒险
time from the same place that's a bit of
a risk
也许是因为，如果其中之一存在制造缺陷，
maybe because presumably if one of them
has a manufacturing defect in it there's
其他人也这样做的好机会，你知道其中一个人容易
a good chance that the other ones do too
you know one of them's prone to
过热，因为您知道的制造商不能提供足够的气流
overheating because the manufacturer you
know didn't provide enough airflow well
可能都是这个问题，所以其中一个过热而死亡，这是一个
it probably all had that problem and so
one of them overheats and dies it's a
其他人也很有可能，所以这是一种相关的失败
good chance that the other ones will too
so that's one kind of correlated failure
您只需要注意另一个是，您知道是否存在
you just have to be careful of another
one is that you know if there's an
地震和我们数据中心所在的城市
earthquake and the city where our
datacenter is probably gonna take out
您知道整个数据中心，我们可以在内部进行所有喜欢的复制
the whole data center you know we can
have all the replication we like inside
该数据中心将无济于事，因为由
that data center it's not going to help
us because the failure caused by an
地震或全市停电或建筑物烧毁
earthquake or a citywide power failure
or something the building burning down
就像我们的副本在该建筑物上时的相关故障一样
is like it's correlated failure between
our replicas if they're on that building
所以如果我们关心地震，那么我们需要把我们的
so if we care about dealing with
earthquakes then we need to put our
复制品也许在不同的城市中，至少在物理上是分开的
replicas in maybe in just different
cities at least physically separate
足以使他们拥有独立的权力，不太可能受到相同权力的影响
enough that they have separate power
unlikely to be affected by the same
自然灾害
natural disaster
好的，但是在本次讨论的背景中，所有这些都是悬停的
okay but that's all sort of hovering in
the background for this discussion where
我们正在谈论的技术，您可能会使用另一个问题
we're talking about the technology you
might use another question about
复制是否值得，您可能会问自己，天哪，您知道这一点
replication is whether it's worthwhile
you may ask yourself gosh you know this
从字面上看，使用这些复制方案时使用的是原来的两倍或三倍
literally uses these replication schemes
use twice as much or three times as much
正确的计算机资源，我们需要让您知道GFS每个文件都有三个副本
computer resources right we need to have
you know GFS had three copies of every
盒子，我们今天要买三倍的磁盘空间
box we have to buy three times as much
disk space the paper for today
您知道复制仅一次，但这意味着我们有两倍的计算机
you know replicates just once but that
means we have twice as many computers
以及CPU和RAM都是昂贵的，真的值得吗
and CPUs and RAM it's all for expensive
like is that really worth it that
费用，您知道那不是我们可以从技术上解决的问题
expense and you know that's not
something we can answer technically
对，这是一个经济问题，取决于拥有
right it's an economic question it
depends on the value of having an
知道您是否在经营银行以及是否会造成后果的可用服务
available service you know if you're
running a bank and if the consequence is
计算机故障是您的客户无法为客户服务
the computer failing is that your
customer you can't serve your customers
而且您无法产生收入，而您的客户都讨厌您，那么这很可能
and you can't generate revenue and your
customers all hate you then it may well
值得一击，你知道每秒多花一万或两万美元
be worth it to blow you know an extra
ten or twenty thousand bucks on a second
电脑，因此如果您是我并且您是
computer so you can have a replica on
the other hand if you're me and you're
运行684 Web服务器，我认为值得一试
running the 684 web server I don't
consider it worthwhile to have a hot
备份84个Web服务器，因为失败的后果非常低，因此
backup of the 84 web server because the
consequences of failure are very low so
复制是否值得您复制多少个副本
the whether the replication is
worthwhile on how many replicas you
应该拥有，您愿意花多少钱，全都关于如何
ought to have and how much you're
willing to spend on it is all about how
大量的成本和不便导致的故障会导致您一切正常
much cost and inconvenience failure
would call it cause you all right this
一开始提到的纸张类型，因为有一些不同的
paper sort of in the beginning mentions
as there's a couple of different
复制方法确实提到了二一二调用状态
approaches to replication really
mentions two one two calls state
转移和其他调用复制状态机的大多数方案
transfer and the other calls replicated
state machine most of the schemes we're
在本课程中要讨论的是复制状态机
going to talk about in this class are
replicated state machines
无论如何，它都会讨论状态转移者背后的想法
it'll talk about both anyway the idea
behind state transferor's that if we
有两个服务器副本，您可以使它们保持同步
have two replicas of a server the way
you cause them to be to stay in sync
这将是实际的副本，以便备份可以拥有所需的一切
that is to be actual replicas so that
the backup can has everything it needs
如果主服务器在状态转移方案中失败，则接管工作方式
to take over if the primary fails in a
state transfer scheme the way that works
是主服务器发送其整个状态的副本，例如
is that the primary sends a copy of its
entire state that is for example the
其RAM的内容备份和备份只是存储
contents of its RAM to the backup and
the backup just sort of stores the
最新状态，因此就可以了，备份中的主要故障都可以
latest state and so it's all there
the primary fails in the backup can
开始以最后一个状态执行，如果主要失败，则得到了所有状态
start executing with this last state it
got if the primary fails so this is all
关于发送主要状态的信息，对于今天（如果今天的话）
about sending the state of the of the
primary and for today's if today's paper
用作状态传输系统，它不会然后我们将成为的状态
worked as a state transfer system which
it doesn't then the state we'd be
谈论的是RAM的内容
talking about would be the contents of
the RAM the contents of the memory of
主要的，所以也许每隔一次，主要的就知道
the primary so maybe every once while
the primary would just you know make a
内存的大副本，并通过网络发送到备份，您可以
big copy of its memory and send it
across the network to the backup you can
想像一下，如果您想提高效率，您知道也许您只会发送
imagine if you wanted to be efficient
you know maybe you would only send the
自您上次发送内存以来更改的内存部分
parts of the memory that it's changed
since the last time you sent in memory
备份复制的状态机
to the backup the replicated state
machine
这种方法观察到大多数服务是大多数计算机设备
this approach observes that most
services are most computer things we
要复制有一些确定性的内部操作，除了
want to replicate have some internal
operation that's deterministic except
当外部输入正确时，您通常会知道是否没有外部输入
when external input comes in right you
know ordinarily if there's no external
对计算机的影响它只执行一条指令
influences on a computer it just
executes one instruction after another
而每条指令所执行的操作是
and what each instruction does is a
deterministic function of what's in the
内存和计算机的寄存器，仅在外部事件发生时
memory and the registers of the computer
and it's only when external events
干预，可能会发生意外情况，例如某个数据包到达
intervene that something unexpected may
happen like a packet arrives of a some
随机的时间，这导致服务器开始做不同的事情我
random time and that causes the server
to start doing something differently I'm
因此，复制状态机方案不会在
so replicated state machine schemes
don't send the state between the
相反，他们只是发送那些他们刚刚发送的外部事件
replicas instead they just send those
external events they just send maybe
从主服务器到备份服务器再发送一些信息，例如从
from a primary to a backup again just
send things like arriving input from the
备份需要了解的外部世界
outside world that the backup needs to
know
观察结果是您知道是否必须拥有两台计算机，并且它们会启动
and the observation is that you know if
you have to two computers and they start
从相同的状态，他们看到相同的输入，以相同的顺序
from the same state and they see the
same inputs that that in the same order
或同时两台计算机仍将是每台计算机的副本
or at the same time the two computers
will continue to be replicas of each
其他和某种执行相同，只要它们在
other and sort of execute identically as
long as they both see the same inputs at
同时，所以这可能转移了内存，并且转移了一些主要的
the same time so this transfers probably
memory and this transfer some primary
仅备份来自客户端或外部外部输入或外部的操作
backup just operations from clients or
external external inputs or external
事件，您知道人们倾向于偏爱复制状态的原因
events and you know the reason why
people tend to favor a replicated state
机器是通常的操作小于状态，但是你知道
machine is that usually operations are
smaller than the state but this you know
服务器的状态（如果是数据库服务器）可能是整个数据库
the state of a server if it's a database
server might be the entire database
可能是您知道千兆字节，而操作只是一些客户端发送的
might be you know gigabytes whereas the
operations are just some clients sending
而且您知道请读或写键27操作通常是小状态
and you know please read or write key 27
operations are usually small the states
通常很大，因此复制状态机通常看起来很吸引人，
usually large so replicate a state
machine usually looks attractive and
轻微的缺点是该方案往往要复杂得多，并且
slight downside is that the schemes tend
to be quite a bit more complicated and
依靠更多有关计算机如何运行的假设，而这
rely on sort of more assumptions about
how the computers operate whereas this
我真的很霸道，我会寄给你我的整个状态
is a really heavy-handed I'm just gonna
send you my whole state sort of a
不用担心有关这些策略的任何问题，是的
nothing to worry about
any questions about these strategies yes
好吧，还好吧，所以问题是假设我们出了点问题
well the did ok so the question is
suppose something went wrong with our
方案和备份实际上与主数据库并不相同，所以您知道
scheme and the backup was not actually
identical to the primary so you know
您以为我们正在运行GFS主站，这是主要的
you're suppose we were running GFS
master and it's the primary it just
分发了至少两个块服务器之一，但是因为这两个您知道，因为
handed out at least two chunks server
one but because the two you know because
我们已经允许主节点的状态与备份所做的不同步
we've allowed the states of the primary
back to drift out of sync the backup did
至少不向任何人都没有发出来的东西，或者有人要过这些东西
not issue at least to anybody it wasn't
even away or anybody had asked for these
所以现在主要的人以为你知道每个人都租了一些块
so now the primary thinks you know
chunks everyone has lease for some chunk
备份中的主故障不会立即接管大块
in the backup doesn't the primary fails
backup takes over right now chunks over
有人认为它有一些租约，但现在的主人没有，
one thinks it has a lease for some chunk
but then the current master doesn't and
很高兴将租约分发给其他中继服务器，现在我们必须分块
is happy to hand out the lease to some
other trunk server now we have to chunk
服务相同的野兽的服务器还可以，所以这只是一个接近家庭的例子，但是
servers serving the same beasts okay so
that's just a close to home example but
真的，您知道几乎所有坏事，而且我认为您会构造任何坏事
really you know almost any bad thing and
kind of I think you construct any bad
通过仅想象一些会混淆错误答案的服务来解决这个问题，因为
scenario by just imagining some service
that confuse the wrong answer because
国家的影响力
the state's leverage
所以你在问随机化
so you're asking about randomization
是的，哦，你们都在谈论这个，我待会儿再说，但这很好
yeah oh y'all talk about this I'll talk
about this a bit later on but it is good
在以下情况下，复制状态方案绝对是最有意义的：
that the replicated state scheme
definitely makes the most sense when the
指令，我们执行的主要对象执行相同的操作
instructions that the primary in the
back of our executing do the same thing
只要没有外部事件发生，那几乎就是对的，
as long as there's no external events
right and that's almost true right you
知道添加指令或其他内容，是的，如果启动，
know for an add instruction or something
yeah you know if the starting if the
相同的内存寄存器，它们都执行它们具有的加法指令
registers of memory of the same and they
both execute an add instruction they had
叛乱分子在相同的产出中具有相同的投入，但在某些地方
insurgents kind of the same inputs in
the same outputs but they're in some
您指出的说明不喜欢，也许有一条说明
instructions as you point out that don't
like maybe there's an instruction that
获取当前的当前时间现在可能会稍微执行一次
gets the current time of day now
probably be executed at slightly
不同的时间或获得当前处理器唯一ID的指令
different times or an instruction that
gets the current processors unique ID
和序列号，它将产生不同的答案，并且
and a serial number it's going to yield
the different answers and the the the
制服回答了听起来像是主要的
uniform answered the questions that
sound like this is that the primary does
它并将答案发送到备份，并且备份不执行该操作
it and sends the answer to the backup
and the backup does not execute that
指令，但在执行该指令的地方
instruction but instead at the point
where it would execute that instruction
它会聆听主要参与者的意见，告诉他们正确答案是正确的
it listens for the primary to tell it
what the right answer would be and just
可以回答我的软件问题的假货
sort of fakes that answer to the
software I'll talk about you know how
尽管今天的VMware计划足够有趣，但可以做到这一点
the VMware scheme does that okay
interestingly enough though today's
论文都是关于复制状态机的，您可能已经注意到
paper is all about a replicated state
machine you may have noticed that
今天的论文只涉及您知道的处理器，目前尚不清楚
today's paper only deals with you know
processors and it's not that clear how
它可以扩展到多核和多核计算机，其中
it could be extended to a multi-core and
a multi-core machine where the
来自两个核心器官的指令的交错是
interleavings of the instructions from
the two cores organ are
非确定性的，所以我们不再在这种情况下出现这种情况
non-deterministic all right so we no
longer have this situation on a
多核计算机，如果我们只让主计算机和备份计算机执行，
multi-core machine where if we just let
the primary and backup execute they're
你知道其他所有条件都是平等的，因为他们不会
you know all else being equal they're
going to be the same because they won't
在多核上执行VMware自此推出了新的可能
execute on multiple cores VMware has
since come out with a new possibly
完全不同的复制系统，可以在多核和新
completely different replication system
that does work on multi-core and the new
在我看来，系统似乎正在使用状态转移而不是复制状态
system appears to me to be using state
transfer instead of replicated state
之所以使用机器，是因为状态转换在面对时更加强大
machine because state transferred is
more robust in the face
多核和并行性（如果您使用计算机并通过您发送内存）
multi-core and parallelism if you use
the machine and send the memory over you
知道内存映像只是机器的状态而已
know that the memory image is just that
just is the state of the machine and
有点无关紧要的是并行性，而复制状态
sort of it doesn't matter that there was
parallelism whereas the replicated state
机器方案确实存在另一个方面的并行性问题
machine scheme really has a problem with
the parallelism you know on the other
我猜测这种新的多核方案更昂贵，好吗
hand I'm guessing that this new
multi-core scheme is more expensive okay
好的，所以如果我们要构建一个复制状态机方案，我们会得到一个
all right so if we want to build a
replicated state machine scheme we got a
要回答的问题数量，因此我们需要确定要达到的级别
number of questions to answer so we need
to decide at what level we're gonna
正确复制状态，那么什么状态我们要担心的是什么状态
replicate state right so what state what
do we mean by state we have to worry
关于主同步和备份同步的正确程度
about how how closely synchronized the
primary and backup have to be right
因为主数据库可能会在备份之前执行一些
because it's likely the primary will
execute a little bit ahead of the backup
毕竟，看到输入的是主要对象，因此备份几乎
after all it it's the primary that sees
the inputs so the backup almost
必须滞后于那，这意味着如果有机会
necessarily must lag over that gives
that means there's an opportunity if the
primary失败，因为prime无法完全追上备份
primary fails for the prime for the
backup not to be fully caught up having
备份实际上实际上与
昂贵，因为它需要很多技巧，所以很多设计很多
expensive because it requires a lot of
chitchat so a lot of designs a lot of
人们汗流is背的是，如果主数据库出现故障，同步有多接近
或者您实际上知道备份是否失败，但是如果主数据库
or you know actually if the backup fails
to but it's more exciting if the primary
失败，必须有某种转换方案，客户端必须
fails there has to be some scheme for
switching over and the clients have to
知道哦，天哪，我现在不应该与服务器一上的旧主服务器说话，我现在应该
know oh gosh I instead of talking to the
old primary on server one I should now
正在与所有客户端的服务器上的备份对话
be talking to the
the backup on server to all the clients
必须以某种方式找出这一点，几乎可以肯定是
have to somehow figure this out the
switch over almost certainly it's almost
不可能设计没有异常的割接系统
impossible maybe impossible to design a
cut over system in which no anomalies
在理想的世界中，您是否知道每一个
are every are ever visible you know in
this sort of ideal world if the primary
感到我们希望没人会注意到没有客户注意到
feels we'd like nobody to ever notice
none of the clients to notice turns out
这基本上是无法达到的，所以在切割过程中会有妈妈的叶子
that's basically unattainable so there's
going to be a mama leaves during the cut
结束之后，我们必须想办法应对他们，最后，如果其中一个
over and we've gotta figure out a way to
cope with them and finally if the one of
如果我们的两个副本之一失败，那么我们真的需要拥有一个新的副本权利
the two if one of our replicas fails we
really need to have a new replica right
如果我们有两个副本而一个失败，那么我们只是靠借来的时间生活
if we have a two replicas and one fails
we're just living on borrowed time right
因为第二个副本可能在某个时候失败，所以我们绝对需要获取
because the second replica may fail at
some point so we absolutely need to get
一个新的副本尽快上线，这可能非常
a new replica back online as fast as
possible so and that can be very
这个国家很大，你知道你知道，但是我们喜欢重复的原因
expensive the state is big you know you
know but the reason we like to replicate
一个状态机是因为我们认为状态转移会很昂贵，但是
a state machine was because we thought
state transfer would be expensive but
复制状态机中的两个副本仍需要具有完整状态
the two replicas in a replicated state
machine still need to have full state
对，如果我们需要创建一个
right we just had a cheap way of keeping
them both in sync if we need to create a
新副本，我们实际上别无选择，只能进行状态转移以创建新副本
new replica we actually have no choice
but state transfer to create the new
复制品，新复制品需要具有状态的完整副本，因此
replicas the new replica needs to have a
complete copy of the state so it's going
创建新副本的成本很高，而且通常人们会花很多钱
to be expensive to create new replicas
and this is often people spending well
实际上人们花很多时间担心所有这些问题，
actually people spend a lot of time
worrying about all these questions and
您知道我们会在查看其他复制状态机时再次看到它们
you know we'll see them again as we look
at other replicated state machine
计划，所以关于什么状态要复制今天的论文的主题有一个非常
schemes so on the topic of what state to
replicate the today's paper has a very
这个问题的有趣答案，它复制了机器的完整状态
interesting answer to this question it
replicates the full state of the machine
那就是所有的内存，所有的机器注册它就像一个非常非常
that is all of memory and all the
Machine registers it's like a very very
详细的复制方案即使最低，也没有什么区别
detailed replication scheme just no
difference at the even of the lowest
备份中主数据库之间的级别，这对于复制而言非常罕见
levels between the primary in the backup
that's quite rare for replication
计划几乎总是你看到的东西是
schemes
almost always you see something that's
更像是GFS，其中GFS绝对不会复制，您知道他们有
more like GFS where GFS absolutely did
not replicate you know they had
复制，但并没有复制您知道的每一个内存
replication but it wasn't replicating
every single you know bit of memory
在主数据库和备份数据库之间，它正在复制更多应用程序
between the primaries and the backups
it was replicating much more application
块的水平表，我知道这种抽象
level table of chunks
I had this abstraction of you know
块和块标识符，这就是它所复制的，不是
chunks and chunk identifiers and that's
what it was replicating it wasn't
复制其他所有东西并不会牺牲
replicating sort of everything else
wasn't going to the expense of
复制机器正在做的其他所有事情
replicating every single other thing
that machines we're doing okay as long
因为他们拥有相同类型的应用程序可见的块集，所以大多数
as they had the same sort of application
visible set of of chunks so most
复制方案在那里走了GFS路线，实际上除了
replication schemes out there go the GFS
route in fact almost everything except
几乎本文和少数几个类似的系统几乎所有
pretty much this paper and a few handful
of similar systems almost everything
在某个级别的应用程序复制级别上使用应用程序，因为
uses application at some level
application level of replication because
它可以更加高效，因为我们不必去做，我们不必去
it can be much more efficient because we
don't have to go to the we don't have to
麻烦例如确保中断恰好发生
go to the trouble of for example making
sure that interrupts occur at exactly
在执行主GFS和备份GFS的同一点不会冒汗
the same point in the execution of the
primary and backup GFS does not sweat
除了这篇文章外，所有其他事情都是必须要做的，因为它的复制量很低
that at all but this paper has to do
because it replicates at such a low
级别，因此大多数人使用特定于应用程序构建高效的系统
level so most people build efficient
systems with applications specific
复制的结果是复制必须
replication the consequence of that
though is that the replication has to be
内置到应用程序权限中，如果您获得
built into the right into the
application right if you're getting a
例如，应用程序级操作的提要确实需要
feed of application level operations for
example you really need to have the
应用程序参与其中，因为某些通用复制之类的东西
application participate in that because
some generic replication thing like
今天的报纸不是真的无法理解
today's paper
doesn't really can't understand the
需要复制的内容的语义
semantics of what needs to be replicated
所以无论如何，大多数团队都是针对特定应用的，例如GFS和其他论文
so anyways so most teams are application
specific like GFS and every other paper
我们将在这个主题上阅读今天的论文是独特的
we're going to read on this topic
today's paper is unique in that it
在计算机级别复制，因此不在乎什么
replicates at the level of the machine
and therefore does not care what
您在其上运行的软件会复制低级内存，并且
software you run on it right it
replicates the low-level memory and
机器注册，您可以在上面运行任何喜欢的软件
machine registers you can run any
software you like on it as long as it
在这种代表的微处理器上运行
runs on that kind of microprocessor
that's being represented this
复制方案适用于该软件可以是任何东西
replication scheme applies to the
software can be anything
而且您知道缺点是效率不一定高
and you know the downside is that it's
not that efficient necessarily the
好处是，您可以使用任何现有软件，甚至可能都不用
upside is that you can take any existing
piece of software maybe you don't even
有它的源代码或了解它的工作原理，并且您知道在某些情况下
have source code for it or understand
how it works and you know do within some
限制，您可以在VMware this复制方案下在此环境下运行它，并且
limits you can just run it under this
under VMware this replication scheme and
它会正常工作，这是任意的魔术容错棒
it'll just work which is sort of magic
fault-tolerance wand for arbitrary
现在就让我先谈谈这是VMware还是Ft的软件
software all right now let me talk about
how this is VMware or Ft first of all
VMware是一家虚拟机公司，他们的业务非常重要
VMware is a virtual machine company
they're what their business is a lot of
他们的业务是销售虚拟机技术以及
their business is selling virtual
machine technology and what virtual
机器指的是您知道自己购买一台计算机并
machines refer to is the idea of you
know you buy a single computer and
而不是在您启动的硬件上启动像Linux这样的操作系统
instead of booting an operating system
like Linux on the hardware you boot
我们将在硬件和虚拟机上调用虚拟机监视器或虚拟机监控程序
we'll call a virtual machine monitor or
hypervisor on the hardware and the
管理程序实际上是模拟多台计算机
hypervisor is job is actually to
simulate multiple multiple computers
该硬件上有多个虚拟机，因此该虚拟机
multiple virtual computers on this piece
of hardware so the virtual machine
监视器可能会启动，您知道一个Linux实例可能是多个
monitor may boot up you know one
instance of Linux may be multiple
Linux实例可以是Windows计算机，也可以是虚拟机
instances of Linux may be a Windows
machine you can the virtual machine
这台计算机上的显示器可以运行一堆不同的操作系统
monitor on this one computer can run a
bunch of different operating systems you
知道它们本身就是某种操作系统内核，然后
know each of these as is itself some
sort of operating system kernel and then
应用程序，所以这是他们开始使用的技术，您知道
applications so this is the technology
they're starting with and you know the
这样做的原因是，如果您知道自己需要，那就证明有很多
reason for this is that if you know you
need to it just turns out there's many
设置此级别的界面非常方便的许多原因
many reasons why it's very convenient to
kind of interpose this level of
硬件和操作系统之间的间接访问，这意味着我们可以
indirection between the hardware and the
operating systems and means that we can
购买一台计算机并在其上运行许多不同的操作系统，我们可以
buy one computer and run lots of
different operating systems on it we can
如果我们运行大量和少量的服务，那么不必拥有
have each if we run lots and lots of
little services instead of having to
有很多计算机每项服务一项，您只需购买一台计算机
have lots and lots of computers one per
service you can just buy one computer
并在操作系统中运行它需要的每个服务，我正在使用他的
and run each service in the operate
system that it needs I'm using his
个人计算机，所以这是他们的起点，他们已经有了
personal machines so this was their
starting point they already had this
东西和围绕它建立的许多复杂的东西
stuff and a lot of sophisticated things
built around it at the start of
设计vmware ft，所以这只是虚拟机，论文内容
designing vmware ft so this is just
virtual machines um what the papers
这样做是要设置一台机器，或者他们确实需要两台机器
doing is that it's gonna set up one
machine or they did requires two
物理机，因为没有必要运行主计算机和备份计算机
physical machines because there's no
point in running the primary and backup
同一物理机上不同虚拟机中的软件，因为
software in different virtual machines
on the same physical machine because
我们正在努力防止硬件故障，所以您至少要
we're trying to guard against hardware
failures so you're gonna to at least you
知道您有两台计算机在运行其虚拟机监视器，而主计算机
know you have two machines running their
virtual machine monitors and the primary
它将在一个备份和另一个备份上运行，因此我们将在其中一台计算机上运行
it's going to run on one the backups and
the other so on one of these machines we
有一个客人，您知道我们只有它可能正在运行许多虚拟机
have a guest you know we only it might
be running a lot of virtual machines we
只关心其中之一，它将运行一些来宾操作系统
only care about one of them it's gonna
be running some guest operating system
还有某种服务器应用程序，例如数据库服务器MapReduce主服务器
and some sort of server application
maybe a database server MapReduce master
之类的东西，所以我将其称为主要设备，然后会有第二台计算机
or something so I'll call this the
primary and there'll be a second machine
您知道运行相同的虚拟机监视器和相同的虚拟机
that you know runs the same virtual
machine monitor and an identical virtual
拥有备份的计算机，因此无论操作系统如何，我们都具有相同的内容
machine holding the backup so we have
the same whatever the operating system
完全一样，虚拟机是您知道给这些来宾吗
is exactly the same and the virtual
machine is you know giving these guest
操作系统的主存储器和备份存储器的每个范围
operating systems the primary and backup
a each range of memory and this memory
图像将是相同的，或者目标是使它们在主图像中相同
images will be identical or the goal is
to make them identical in the primary in
在备份中，我们有两台物理机，每台物理机运行一个虚拟机
the backup we have two physical machines
each one of them running a virtual
机器来宾拥有自己关心的服务副本，我们假设
machine guest with a its own copy of the
service we care about we're assuming
有一个网络连接这两台机器，此外
that there's a network connecting these
two machines and in addition on this
除了这个网络之外，还有一些客户端
local area network in addition on this
network there's some set of clients
真的，他们不必成为客户，他们可能只是其他计算机
really they don't have to be clients
they're just maybe other computers that
我们的复制服务需要与其中一些我们的客户交谈
our replicated service needs to talk
with some of them our clients
发送请求结果在本文中有复制服务
sending requests it turns out in this
paper there the replicated service
实际上不使用本地磁盘，而是假设存在某种
actually doesn't use a local disk and
instead assumes that there's some sort
与他对话的磁盘服务器，虽然很难
of disk server that it talks to him
although it's a little bit hard to
从本文中意识到这一点，该方案实际上并没有真正对待
realize this from the paper the scheme
actually does not really treat the de
尤其是服务器，它只是数据包的另一个外部来源，
server particularly especially it's just
another external source of packets and
复制状态机可能不会发送数据包的地方
place that the replicated state machine
may send packets do not very much
与客户不同，所以基本方案是我们假设这些
different from clients okay so the basic
scheme is that the we assume that these
我们的确切两个虚拟机的两个副本
two replicas the two virtual machines
primary and backup are our exact
复制一些您知道的客户端，数据库客户端知道谁拥有一些客户端
replicas some client you know database
client who knows who has some client of
我们的复制服务器向主服务器发送一个请求，这实际上需要
our replicated server sends a request to
the primary and that really takes the
我们正在谈论的网络数据包形式会生成一个
form of a network packet that's what
we're talking about that generates an
中断，此中断实际上进入
interrupt
and this interrupts actually goes to the
虚拟机至少在第一个实例中监视虚拟机
virtual machine monitor at least in the
first instance the virtual machine
监视器看到热点，这是此复制服务的输入，因此
monitor sees a hot here's the input for
this replicated service and so the
虚拟机监视器做两件事，一是模拟网络
virtual machine monitor does two things
one is it sort of simulates a network
数据包到达中断进入主客户机操作系统以
packet arrival interrupt into the
primary guest operating system to
将其交付给应用程序的主副本，并附加到虚拟
deliver it to the primary copy of the
application and in addition the virtual
您知道的计算机监视器知道这是复制的虚拟机的输入
machine monitor you know knows that this
is an input to a replicated virtual
机器，因此它将网络上的数据包副本发送回
machine and it's so it sends back out on
the network a copy of that packet to the
备份虚拟机监视器，它也在猜测和备份虚拟机
backup virtual machine monitor it's also
guessing and backup virtual machine
监视器知道热点是此特定复制状态机的数据包，并且
monitor knows a hot is a packet for this
particular replicated state machine and
它还在备份时伪造了某种网络数据包到达中断，并且
it also fakes a sort of network packet
arrival interrupt at the backup and
传递数据包，所以现在主数据包和背面都有此副本
delivers the packet so now both the
primary and the back have a copy this
数据包，它们看起来像是您知道的相同输入，其中包含很多细节
packet they looks at the same input you
know with a lot of details are gonna
以相同的方式处理并保持同步
process it in the same way and stay
synchronized
当然，服务可能会在主服务器上回复客户
course the service is probably going to
reply to the client on the primary the
服务将生成一个回复数据包，并将其发送到虚拟
service will generate a reply packet and
send it on the NIC that the virtual
计算机监视器正在仿真，然后虚拟机监视器或
machine monitor is emulating and then
the virtual machine monitor or will
我们会在主服务器上看到该输出数据包，他们实际上会发送回复
we'll see that output packet on the
primary they'll actually send the reply
在网络上返回到客户端，因为备份运行正常
back out on the network to the client
because the backup is running exactly
相同的指令序列也会产生一个回复数据包
the same sequence of instructions it
also generates a reply packet back to
客户端并在其模拟的NIC上发送该回复数据包，这是虚拟的
the client and sends that reply packet
on its emulated NIC it's the virtual
模拟该网络接口卡的机器监视器，它说aha
machine monitor that's emulating that
network interface card and it says aha
您知道虚拟机监视器说我知道这只是备份
you know the virtual machine monitor
says I know this was the backup only the
允许primary生成输出，并且虚拟机监视器删除
primary is allowed to generate output
and the virtual machine monitor drops
回复数据包，所以他们两个都看到输入，只有主生成
the reply packet so both of them see
inputs and only the primary generates
就术语而言，输出就是本文所说的输入事件流
outputs as far as terminology goes the
paper calls this stream of input events
其他我们将在信息流中谈论的其他事件称为
and other things other events we'll talk
about from the stream is called the
日志通道大概都通过相同的网络，但是这些事件
logging Channel it all goes over the
same network presumably but these events
自从我们在日志通道上调用日志事件后部开始的主要事件
the primary since the back of our called
log events on the log Channel
容错能力的来源是那些主要的崩溃
where the fault tolerance comes in is
that those the primary crashes what the
备份将要看到的是，它停止获取日志时停止获取东西
backup is going to see is that it stops
getting stuff on the stops getting log
日志条目停止在日志记录通道上获取日志条目，我们
entries a log entry stops getting log
entries on the logging channel and we
知道事实证明，备份可以期望每秒获得很多备份，因为
know it it turns out that the backup can
expect to get many per second because
生成日志条目的原因之一是周期性的定时器中断
one of the things that generates log
entries is periodic timer interrupts in
在主节点中，每个中断都会产生一个中断
the in the primary each one of which
turns out every interrupt generates a
将日志条目记录到备份中，这些计时器中断将发生，如100
log entries into the backup these timer
interrupts are going to happen like 100
每秒一次，因此备份当然可以期望看到
times a second so the backups can
certainly expect to see
如果主要的话，日志通道上的大量选择
a lot of chitchat on the logging Channel
if the primaries up if the primary
崩溃，然后在此监视的虚拟机会说“天哪”
crashes then the virtual machine
monitored over here will say gosh you
知道我已经一秒钟没有收到任何日志记录
know I haven't received anything on the
logging channel for like a second or
但是，主要对象必须死了多长时间，或者在某种情况下，
however long the primary must be dead or
or something and in that case when the
备份停止从主要纸张查看日志条目
backup stop seeing log entries from the
primary the paper the way the paper
冻结的是后台运行，这意味着它停止了
freezes it is that the back of goes live
and what that means is that it stops
在主记录和记录记录通道上等待这些输入事件
waiting for these input events on the
logging Channel from the primary and
相反，此虚拟机监视器仅允许该备份自由执行
instead this virtual machine monitor
just lets this backup execute freely
无需等待，不受主vmm的输入事件的驱动
without waiting for without being driven
by input events from the primary the vmm
对网络做某事，以使将来的客户端请求转到
does something to the network to cause
future client requests to go to the
备份而不是主备份，并且此处的VMM停止丢弃备份
backup instead of the primary and the
VMM here stops discarding the backup
人员，这是主要的，不是备份停止丢弃此输出
personnel it's the primary not the
backup stops discarding output from this
虚拟机，所以现在这个或机器直接获取输入，并且有一个
virtual machine so now this or machine
directly gets the inputs and there's a
大量的产品输出，现在我们的备份已接管，类似地，您知道
lot of produce output and now our backup
is taken over and similarly you know
这不太有趣，但必须正常工作
that this is less interesting but has to
work correctly
如果备份失败，则类似的主数据库必须使用类似的过程来放弃
if the backup fails a similar primary
has to use a similar process to abandon
备份停止向其发送事件，而其行为更像是一次
the backup stop sending it events and
just sort of act much more like a single
非复制服务器，因此其中一个可以上线，如果另一个
non replicated server so either one of
them can go live if the other one
似乎已经停止，您知道停止产生网络流量
appears to be dead stops you know stops
generating network traffic
魔术现在取决于您知道，取决于网络技术是什么
magic now it depends you know depends on
what the networking technology is I
与本文一起思考的一种可能性是，它每个都坐在以太网上
think with the paper one possibility is
that this is sitting on Ethernet every
Internet上的物理计算机或实际上每个网卡都有一个48位唯一ID
physical computer on the Internet or
really every NIC has a 48 bit unique ID
我现在正在弥补这个问题，实际上可能不是每个物理
I'm making this up now the it could be
that in fact instead of each physical
每个虚拟机都有唯一ID的计算机，以及备份何时进行
computer having a unique ID each virtual
machine does and when the backup takes
基本上，它声称主服务器的以太网ID是自己的，并且启动
over it essentially claims the primary's
Ethernet ID as its own and it starts
说您知道我是该ID的所有者，然后是以太网上的其他人
saying you know I'm the owner of that ID
and then other people on the ethernet
将开始向我们发送数据包，这是设计师认为的我的解释
will start sending us packets that's my
interpretation the designers believed
他们已经确定了所有这些来源，并且对于每个来源，
they had identified all such sources and
for each one of them the primary does
无论您知道什么，执行随机数生成器指令或
whatever it is you know executes the
random number generator instruction or
有时会中断一次备份，而备份和虚拟备份
机器监视器会检测到任何此类指令并拦截该指令，并且
machine monitor sort of detects any such
instruction and and intercepts that and
没有这样做，他说，备份中的事件是备用的
doesn't do it and he said the backup
wheats for an event on the logging
频道说这个指令号你知道随机数是什么
Channel saying this instruction number
you know the random number was whatever
它在主要
it was on the primary
埃德维希是是
Edwige
yes yes
是的，该论文暗示他们让英特尔向微处理器添加了功能，以便
yeah the paper hints that they got Intel
to add features to the microprocessor to
完全支持这一点，但他们不说还可以
support exactly this but they don't say
what it was okay
好吧，关于那个话题，到目前为止，你知道这个故事是一种假设
okay so on that topic the so far that
you know the story is sort of assumed
只要备份从客户端看到软件包，它就会执行
that as long as the backup to sees the
package from the clients it'll execute
与初级相同，实际上掩盖了一些巨大的
in identically to the primary and that's
actually glossing over some huge and
重要细节，所以一个问题是，正如几个人提到的那样
important details so one problem is that
as a couple of people have mentioned
有些事情是不确定的，现在不是这样
there are some things that are
non-deterministic now it's not the case
计算机中发生的每件事都是确定性功能
that every single thing that happens in
the computer is a deterministic function
计算机内存的内容是一种直
of the contents of the memory of the
computer it is for a sort of straight
行代码执行通常但不一定总是那么担心
line code execution often but certainly
not always so worried about is things
这可能不是当前状态的严格函数
that may happen that are not a strict
function of the current state that is
如果我们在主数据库和备份数据库上不谨慎，可能会有所不同，因此
that might be different if we're not
careful on the primary and backup so
这些是可能会发生的不确定事件，因此设计师
these are sort of non-deterministic
events that may happen so the designers
只好坐下来，想弄清楚他们都在做什么，这里是那些
had to sit down and like figure out what
they all work and here are the ones
他们谈论的是这种东西，其中之一是来自外部的输入
here's the kind of stuff they talked
about so one is inputs from external
像客户这样的资源，只要他们正确到达就可以到达
sources like clients which arrive just
whenever they arrive right they're not
可预见的，没有任何时间客户请求
predictable there are no sense in which
the time at which a client request
到达或其内容是服务的确定性功能
arrives or its content is a
deterministic function of the services
状态，因为事实并非如此，因此实际上这些系统实际上专用于
state because it's not so these actually
this system is really dedicated to a
服务只能通过网络进行通信的世界，因此唯一真正的
world in which services only talk over
the network and so the only really
基本上，该系统中输入或输出的唯一形式是
basically the only form of input or
output in this system is supported by
这个系统似乎是网络数据包来来去去，所以我们没有放
this system seems to be network packets
coming and going so we didn't put
到达真正意味着它是一个小包的地方
arrives at what that really means it's a
packet
到达，数据包真正为我们组成的是
arrives and what a packet really
consists of for us is the data in the
数据包加上表明该数据包已发出的中断
packet plus the interrupt
that's signaled that the packet had
到达，所以这很重要，所以当数据包到达时
arrived so that's quite important so
when a packet arrives
我通常是将NIC DMA的数据包内容存入内存，然后引发
I'm ordinarily the NIC DMA is the packet
contents into memory and then raises an
操作系统感觉到的中断，并且中断发生在某些地方
interrupt which the operating system
feels and the interrupt happens at some
指向指令流，因此两者在外观上必须相同
point in the instruction stream and so
both of those have to look identical on
主要和备份，否则我们将要执行死刑
the primary and backup or else we're
gonna have they're also executions gonna
发散，所以您知道真正的问题是何时中断恰好发生在
diverge and so you know the real issue
is when the interrupt occurs exactly at
哪条指令恰好发生了中断，并且最好在
which instruction the interrupts happen
to occur and better be the same on the
备份中的主要对象，否则它们的执行方式和状态不同
primary in the backup otherwise their
execution is different and their states
会发散，所以我们关心数据包的内容和时间
are gonna diverge and so we care about
the content of the packet and the timing
中断，然后正如几个人提到的那样，
of the interrupt and then as a couple of
people have mentioned there's a few
在不同计算机上行为不同的说明，或
instructions that that behave
differently on different computers or
取决于诸如随机数生成器之类的东西
differently depending on something like
there's maybe a random number generator
指令，我会得到一天中不同时间的指令
instruction there's I get time-of-day
instructions that will yield different
答案在不同时间调用，并且唯一的ID指令又一个巨大的优势
answers have called at different times
and unique ID instructions another huge
本文基本排除的不确定性来源是多核的
source of non determinism which the
paper basically rules out is multi-core
并行性是一个单元过程或仅是系统，因此没有多核
parallelism is a unit process or only
system there's no multi-core in this
世界上这样做的原因是，如果它允许多核，那么该服务
world the reason for this is that if it
allowed multi-core then then the service
将在多个内核上运行，其余的服务说明
would be running on multiple cores and
the instructions of the service the rest
你们知道不同的核心以某种方式交错
of you know the different cores are
interleaved in some way which is not
可预测的，因此如果我们在备份的
predictable and so really if we run the
same code on the on the backup in the
服务器，如果它是在多核上运行的并行代码，那么tubo将
server if it's parallel code running on
a multi-core the tubo interleave the
硬件将以不同方式在两个内核中执行指令
instructions in the two cores in
different ways the hardware will and
可能会导致不同的结果，因为您知道
that can just cause
different results because you know
假设代码和您知道的两个核心都要求锁定某些
supposing the code and the two cores you
know they both asked for a lock on some
您知道主机上的数据很好，内核一可能在内核2之前获得了锁定
data well on the master you know
core one may get the lock before Core 2
在奴隶上只是因为一个微小的时序差异核心可能
on the slave just because of a tiny
timing difference core to may got the
首先锁定，您知道执行结果可能完全不同
lock first and the you know execution
results are totally different likely to
如果不同的线程获得锁，则完全不同
be totally different if different
threads get the lock
所以多核是不确定性的严峻根源。
so multi-core is the grim source of
non-determinism man is just totally
在这篇论文世界中是非法的，而且实际上就我所知
outlawed in this papers world and indeed
like as far as I can tell the techniques
不太适用该服务不能使用多核并行
are not really applicable the service
can't use multi-core parallel
并行性几乎可以肯定，硬件是多核并行的，但这是
parallelism the hardware is almost
certainly multi-core parallel but that's
位于虚拟机下面的硬件会监视该计算机，
the hardware sitting underneath the
virtual machine monitor the machine that
虚拟机监视器向来宾操作系统之一公开
the virtual machine monitor exposes to
one of the guest operating systems that
运行模拟虚拟机的主备份是一个独角兽，它是一个单元
runs the primary backup that emulated
virtual machine is a unicorn it's a unit
本文中的处理器机器，我想这不是一个简单的方法
processor machine in this paper and I'm
guessing there's not an easy way for
他们使该设计适应多核虚拟机
them to adapt this design to multi-core
virtual machines
好，所以这些真的就是这些事件
okay so so these are really it's it's
it's these events that go over the
日志记录通道，因此日志的格式记录了他们没有的日志记录条目
logging channel and so the format of a
log record a log log entry they don't
可以这么说，但我猜想日志条目中确实有三件事
quite say but I'm guessing that there's
really three things in a log entry
有发生事件的指令号，因为如果您
there's the instruction number at which
the event occurred because if you're
传递中断，或者您知道输入或传递更好的信息
delivering an interrupt or you know
input or whatever it better be delivered
在主备份中的完全相同的位置，因此我们需要了解
at exactly the same place in the primary
backup so we need to know the
指令号和按指令号的意思是您知道
instruction number and by instruction
number I mean you know the number of
自机器启动以来的指令，为什么不是指令地址而是
instructions since the Machine booted
why not the instruction address but like
哦，或者自启动以来执行40亿条和第79条指令，所以登录
oh or executing the four billion and
79th instructions since boot so log
条目将有指令号4的中断输入
entry is going to have instruction
number four an interrupt for input it's
将成为在主节点上传递中断的指令
going to be the instruction at which the
interrupt was delivered on the primary
而对于像get这样的怪异指令，它将是
and for a weird instruction like get at
time of day it's going to be the
一天中获取时间的指令的指令号
instruction number of the instruction of
the get time of day or whatever
在主数据库上执行的指令，以便您了解备份
instruction that was executed on the
primary so that you know the backup
知道在哪里调用此事件会发生，所以会有一种类型
knows where to where to call this event
to occur okay so there's gonna be a type
你知道网络输入什么怪异的指令，然后我要
you know network input whatever a weird
instruction and then there's I'm gonna
是数据包到达的数据，它将是这些数据包之一的数据包数据
be data for a packet arrival it's gonna
be the packet data for one of these
奇怪的指令，它将是指令的结果
weird instructions it's going to be the
result of the instruction when it was
在主数据库上执行，以便备份虚拟机可以伪造
executed on the primary so that the
backup virtual machine can sort of fake
指令并提供相同的结果
the instruction and supply that same
result
好的，以这两个操作系统为例
okay so so as an example the both of
these operating systems guest operating
系统假定要求硬件在这种情况下是仿真硬件
system assumes requires that the
hardware in this case emulated hardware
虚拟机有一个计时器，每秒滴答百次，并导致
virtual machine has a timer that ticks
say a hundred times a second and causes
中断操作系统，这就是操作系统保持的方式
interrupts to the operating system and
that's how the operating system keeps
通过计数这些计时器中断来跟踪时间，以便播放
track of time it's by counting these
timer interrupts so the way that plays
记下那些计时器，注意为什么它们必须在完全相同的位置发生
out those timer notice why they have to
happen at exactly the same place in the
主要和备份，否则它们将不会执行相同的操作而不会产生差异
primary and backup otherwise they don't
execute the same no diverge so what
真正发生的是物理机上有一个计时器
really happens is that the there's
there's a timer on the physical machine
运行Ft虚拟机监视器和物理上的计时器
that's running the Ft virtual machine
monitor and the timer on the physical
机器滴答作响并向计时器传递中断，直到虚拟机为止
machine ticks and delivers an interrupt
a timer and up to the virtual machine
在主虚拟机上监视您所知道的
monitor on the primary the virtual
machine monitor at you know the
适当的时候停止执行主要记录
appropriate moment stops the execution
of the primary writes down the
自启动以来您所知道的指令号，然后
instruction number that it was at you
know instruction since boot and then
在来宾操作中提供各种伪造的模拟和中断
delivers sort of fake simulates and
interrupts into the guest operating
系统在主要指令号上说哦，你知道
system in the primary at that
instruction number saying oh you know
您正在仿真计时器刚刚打勾的硬件
you're emulating the timer Hardware just
ticked
有中断，然后主虚拟机监视器发送
there's the interrupt and then the
primary virtual machine monitor sends
您知道中断发生的那个指令号
that instruction number which the
interrupt happened you know to the
备份当然，其虚拟机监视器的备份也需要计时器
backup the backup of course it's virtual
machine monitor is also taking timer
从其物理计时器中断，它没有给他们，也没有给他们
interrupts from its physical timer and
it's not giving them it's not giving
这是真正的物理计时器中断到它的备份操作系统
it's a real physical timer interrupts to
the to the backup operating system it's
只是不理会它们，当法律为原始计时器的日志条目时
just ignoring them when the law when the
log entry for the primaries timer
中断到达此处，则备份虚拟机监视器将安排
interrupts arrives here then the backup
virtual machine monitor will arrange
CPU，这需要特殊的CPU支持才能导致物理
with the CPU and this requires special
CPU support to cause the physical
机器以相同的指令号中断
machine to interrupt at the same
instruction number
在定时器中断时，虚拟的
at the timer interrupts tapped into the
primary at that point the virtual
机器监视器再次从来宾那里获得控制权，然后伪造计时器
machine monitor gets control again from
the guest and then fakes the timer
现在进入备份操作系统的中断完全相同
interrupts into the backup operating
system now exact exactly the same
指令号，因为它发生在主要井上，所以观察
instruction number as it occurred on the
primary well yeah so the observation is
这将取决于其中具有一些特殊硬件的CPU，
that this will this relies on the CPU
having some special hardware in it where
vmm可以告诉硬件CPU请从中中断一千条指令
the vmm can tell the hardware CPU please
interrupt a thousand instructions from
有时，您会知道vmm在哪里，以便您知道它会在
now and then the vmm you know where so
that you know it'll interrupt at the
正确的指令号与主要指令相同，然后
right instruction number the same
instruction as the primary did and then
vmm只是告诉CPU启动X，然后在备份中再次执行，并且
the vmm just tells the cpu to start X
resume executing again in the backup and
恰好一千条指令之后，CPU会强制中断进入
exactly a thousand instructions later
the CPU will force an interrupt into the
虚拟机监视器，那是特殊的硬件，但事实证明是
virtual machine monitor and that that's
special hardware but it turns out it's
您知道所有Intel芯片上的产品，所以它不是不是那么特别
you know on all Intel chips so it's not
it's not that special anymore you know
15年前它是异国情调的，现在已经完全正常了，事实证明那里
15 years ago it was exotic now it's
totally normal and it turns out there's
如果您想进行剖析，还可以使用其他许多类似um的方法
a lot of other uses for it like um if
you want to do profiling you wanna do
CPU时间性能分析您真正想要的东西或一种进行CPU时间性能分析的方法
CPU time profiling what you'd really
like or one way to do CPU time profiling
是让微处理器每千条指令中断一次，
is to have the microprocessor interrupt
every thousand instructions right and
这是硬件，这是硬件，这也是相同的硬件
this is the hardware that's this
Hardware also this is the same hardware
这将导致微处理器每千次产生一个中断
that would cause the microprocessor to
generate an interrupt every thousand
指令，因此它是CPU中非常自然的一种小工具
instructions so it's a very natural sort
of gadget to want in your CPU
好的，是的
all right yes
如果备份优先于主数据库，那该怎么办？
what if the backup gets ahead of the
primary so you know we standing above
知道哦，您知道主要对象即将在
know that oh you know the primary is
about to take an interrupt at the
第百万条指令，但是备份已经是您知道执行的百万分之一
millionth instruction but the backup is
already you know executed the millionth
和第一条指令，所以如果我们让这种情况发生，那也将会是
and first instruction so it's gonna be
if we let this happen it's gonna be too
如果让备份xu成为主要节点的负责人，则延迟交付中断
late to deliver the interrupts if we let
the backup xu the head of the primary
在同一时刻传递中断将为时已晚。
it's going to be too late to deliver the
interrupts at the same point in the
主指令流和指令流的备份，因此我们
primary instruction stream and the
backup of the instruction stream so we
不能让这种情况发生，我们不能让备份领先于主要
cannot let that happen we cannot let the
backup get ahead of the primary in
执行和VMware aft做的方式就是备份虚拟
execution and the way VMware aft does
that is that the the backup virtual
机器监视器实际上保留了等待事件的缓冲区
machine monitor it actually keeps a
buffer of waiting events that have
从主服务器到达，除非有
arrived from the primary and it will not
let to the backup execute unless there's
该缓冲区中至少有一个事件，如果该缓冲区中有一个事件，则它
at least one event in that buffer and if
there's one event in that buffer then it
从指令号可以知道它受力的位置
will know from the instruction number
the place at which it's got a force the
备份停止执行，因此始终始终使用
backup to stop executing so always
always the backup is executing with the
准确告知CPU下一条指令的下一个停止点
CPU being told exactly where the next
stopping point the next instruction
停止点的数量是因为备份仅在其具有
number of a stopping point is because
the backup only executes if it has a an
这里的事件告诉它下一步在哪里停止，这意味着它在之后启动
event here that tells it where to stop
next so that means it starts up after
主数据库，因为备份甚至要等到主数据库才能开始执行
the primary because the backup can't
even start executing until the primary
已经生成了第一个事件，而该事件已经到达备份，因此
has generated the first event and that
event has arrived at the backup so the
基本上总是在至少一个事件之后的一个事件的备份类型
backup sort of always one event
basically behind the at least one event
落后于主要学校，如果出于某些其他原因而较慢
behind the primary and if it's slower
for some other whatever reason maybe
该物理机上还有其他东西在运行，则备份可能
there's other stuff running on that
physical machine then the backup might
让您了解主要事件背后的多个事件
get you know multiple events behind at
the primary
好吧，关于到达特定案例的过程有些混乱
alright there's a one little piece of
mess about arriving the specific case of
通常在数据包从网络接口到达时到达数据包
arriving packets ordinarily when a
packet arrives from a network interface
如果我们没有运行虚拟机，则网络接口卡将
card if we weren't running a virtual
machine the network interface card would
将数据包内容通过DMA传输到其所连接的计算机的内存中
DMA the packet content into the memory
of the computer that it's attached to
当数据从网络接口卡到达时，这意味着
sort of as the data arrives from the
network interface card and that means
您知道您永远不应该编写这样的软件，但是可能是因为
you know you should never write software
like this but it could be that the
在计算机上运行的操作系统实际上可能会看到
operating system that's running on a
computer might actually see the data of
数据包作为其DMA或从网络接口卡复制到内存中
a packet as its DMA or copied from the
network interface card into memory right
你知道这是，你知道我们不知道这个操作系统是什么
you know this is and you know we don't
know what operating this system is
经过精心设计，使其可以支持任何操作系统，而且成本可能很高
designed so that it can support any
operating system and cost maybe there is
监视内存中到达的数据包的操作系统
an operating system that watches
arriving packets in memory as they're
复制到内存中，所以我们不能让它发生，因为如果主发生
copied into memory so we can't let that
happen because if the primary happens to
在玩这个技巧，它将让您知道我们是否允许网络接口
be playing that trick it's gonna see you
know if we allowed the network interface
卡直接将DMA传入数据包输入主存储器
card to directly DMA incoming packets
into the memory of the primary the
最主要的是，我们无法控制何时投放网络的确切时间
primary we don't have any control over
the exact timing of when the network
接口卡将数据复制到内存中，因此我们不会知道
interface card copies data into memory
and so we're not going to know sort of
主服务器什么时候观察或未观察到来自数据包的数据
at what times the primary did or didn't
observe data from the packet arriving
所以这意味着实际上NIC将传入的数据包复制到
and so what that means is that in fact
the NIC copies incoming packets into
虚拟机监视器的专用内存，然后是网络接口
private memory of the virtual machine
monitor and then the network interface
卡中断虚拟机监视器并说哦，数据包已到达
card interrupts the virtual machine
monitor and says oh a packet has arrived
此时，虚拟机监视器将挂起主服务器和
at that point the virtual machine
monitor will suspend the primary and
记住在复制整个数据包到
remember what instruction number had
suspended at copy the entire packet into
主存储器挂起且不查看此副本时的主存储器
the primaries memory while the primary
suspended and not looking at this copy
然后将网络接口卡中断模拟为主
and then emulate a network interface
card interrupt into the primary
然后将数据包和指令号发送到备份
and then send the packet and the
instruction number to the backup the
备份也会挂起您知道虚拟机监视器将要备份的备份绳
backup will also suspend the backup rope
you know virtual machine monitor will
将备份花费在该指令号上，然后再次复制整个数据包
spend the backup at that instruction
number copy the entire packet and again
保证不观看数据到达后再备份
to the back-up is guaranteed not to be
watching the data arrive and then fakin
以相同的指令号中断主程序，这是
interrupts at the same instruction
numbers the primary and this is the
在文件中解释了一些反弹缓冲机制，是的，
something the bounce buffer mechanism
explained in the paper okay yeah the the
仅说明而导致记录通道流量或很奇怪
only instructions and that result in
logging channel traffic or are weird
很少有指令的指令可能会产生
instructions which are rare no its
instructions that might yield a
如果在主数据库和备用数据库上执行类似的结果，则结果不同
different result if executed on the
primary and backup like instruction to
获取当前时间或当前处理器号或询问多少
get the current time of day or current
processor number or ask how many
指令已被执行，或者实际上是相对而言
instructions have been executed or and
those actually turn out to be relatively
难得的是，当某些机器问或
rare there's also one them to get random
tasks when some machines to ask or a
硬件生成用于密码学或其他的随机数，但那些
hardware generated random number for
cryptography or something and but those
不是日常的说明，大多数说明，例如添加说明
are not everyday instructions most
instructions like add instructions
他们将在小学获得相同的结果
they're gonna get the same result on
primary and that go
是的，因此备份中复制这些文件的方式只是转发
yeah so the way those get replicated on
the back up is just by forwarding that's
完全正确地打包和转发每个网络数据包
exactly right each network packet just
it's packaged up and forwarded as it is
作为网络数据包，并由tcp / ip协议栈解释为您知道
as a network packet and is interpreted
by the tcp/ip stack on both you know so
我预计99.99％的日志记录通道流量将成为传入数据包
I'm expecting 99.99% of the logging
channel traffic to be incoming packets
而只有一小部分来自特殊的不确定性结果
and only a tiny fraction to be results
from special non-deterministic
说明，因此我们可以猜测流量负载可能是多少
instructions and so we can kind of guess
what the traffic load is likely to be
对于基本上为客户服务的服务器，它是每个客户的副本
for for a server that serves clients
basically it's a copy of every client
数据包，然后我们就会知道什么记录通道，记录速度有多快
packet and then we'll sort of know what
the logging channel how fast the logging
频道必须没事，所以值得谈论一下
channel has to be all right so um so
it's worth talking a little bit about
输出是如何工作的，在这个系统中，实际上基本上是唯一的输出
how output works and in this system
really the only what output basically
表示仅发送客户端发送请求的数据包作为网络
means only is sending packets that
client send requests in as network
响应作为网络数据包返回，实际上没有
packets the response goes back out as
network packets and there's really no
我提到的其他形式的输出您知道主计算和备份计算
other form of output as I mentioned the
you know both primary and backup compute
他们想要发送的输出数据包，并要求模拟混合到
the output packet they want to send and
that sort of asks that simulated mix to
发送实际上在主数据库上发送的数据包，然后将其丢弃
send the packet it's really sent on the
primary and simply discard it the output
数据包在备份中被丢弃了，但是事实证明还多了
packet discarded on the backup okay but
it turns out is a little more
比那要复杂的多，因此假设我们正在运行的是某种
complicated than that so supposing we're
what we're running is a some sort of
简单的数据库服务器和操作我们的数据库的客户端操作
simple database server and the operation
the client operation that our database
服务器支持增量，客户端发送增量请求的想法
server supports is increment and ideas
the client sends an increment requests
数据库服务器增加该值并发送回新值，因此可能在
the database server increments the value
and sends back the new value so maybe on
主要井到目前为止，一切都很好，主要备份都
the primary well let's say everything's
fine so far and the primary backup both
内存中有值10，这是计数器的当前值，还有一些
have value 10 in memory and that's the
current value at the counter and some
局域网上的客户端发送一个您知道的增量请求给
client on the local area network sends a
you know an increment request to
数据包是主要的，您知道传送到主要是
the primary that packet is you know
delivered to the primary it's you know
它执行了主服务器软件，主服务器说哦
it's executed the primary server
software and the primary says oh you
知道当前值10我将更改为11并发送您知道的响应
know current values 10 I'm gonna change
to 11 and send a you know response
包发回给客户，说11作为他们回复与我相同的请求
packet back to the client saying saying
11 as their reply the same request as I
提到应该发送到备份的内容也将在此处处理
mentioned gonna supposed to be sent to
the backup will also be processed here
它将10更改为11也将生成回复，我们将其丢弃
it's going to change this 10 to 11 also
generate a reply and we'll throw it away
这就是应该发生的输出，但是您还需要询问
that's what's supposed to happen the
output however you also need to ask
如果您应该在尴尬的时间发生故障，该怎么办
yourself what happens if there's a
failure at an awkward time if you should
总是在这个班上应该总是问自己，最尴尬的时间是什么
always in this class should always ask
yourself what's the most awkward time to
有一个失败，失败会发生什么，然后假设
have a failure and what would happen you
to failure occurred then so suppose the
primary确实的确会在这里将回复返回给客户端，但是客户端
primary does indeed generate the reply
here back to the client but the client
在将报告的回复发送给客户端后，主要数据库就会崩溃，并且
the primary crashes just after sending
the report its reply to the client and
更糟的是，事实证明您知道这只是一个网络
furthermore and much worse it turns out
that you know this is just a network it
不能保证传递数据包，让我们假设此日志条目位于
doesn't guarantee to deliver packets
let's suppose this log entry on the
当主要节点死亡时，日志记录通道也下降了，所以现在
logging channel got dropped also when
the when the primary died so now the
播放状态是客户收到回复说11，但备份没有
state of play is the client received a
reply saying 11 but the backup did not
获取客户端请求，因此其状态仍然为10，现在备份将接管
get the client request so its state is
still 10 no now the backup takes over
因为抓住了，主要的已经死了，这个客户或其他一些客户
because it's seized the primary is dead
and this client or maybe some other
客户端发送一个增量请求一个新的备份，现在它正在处理
client sends an increment request a new
backup and now it's really processing
这些请求，因此当新备份获得下一个增量请求时
these requests and so the new backup
when it gets the next increment requests
您知道它现在将其状态更改为11并生成第二个11
you know it's now going to change its
state to 11 and generate a second 11
响应可能是同一客户，也可能是另一客户，如果客户
response maybe the same client maybe to
a different client which if the clients
比较笔记，或者如果它是同一客户，则显然不可能发生
compare notes or if it's the same client
it's just obviously cannot have happened
我不是这样，您知道吗，因为我们必须支持能够
I didn't so you know because we have to
support unmodified software that does
不该有任何有趣的事情
not
damn that there's any funny business of
复制正在进行，这意味着我们没有机会知道你
replication going on that means we do
not have the opportunity to you know you
可以想象客户会走，你知道我们可以改变客户以实现
can imagine the client could go you know
we could change the client to realize
容错发生了一些有趣的事情，我不知道是什么
something funny it happened with the
fault tolerance and do I don't know what
但是我们这里没有那个选项，因为整个系统实际上只是
but we don't have that option here
because this whole system really only
如果我们运行未经修改的软件是有道理的，所以这很大，这是一个
makes sense if we're running unmodified
software so so this was a big this is a
灾难我们不能让这种情况发生，有人从报纸上记得吗
disaster we can't have let this happen
does anybody remember from the paper how
他们防止这种情况发生，是的，所以您要这样做
they prevent this from happening the
output rule yeah so you want to do you
知道，所以输出规则是解决该问题的方法，
know yeah so the output rules is the
their solution to this problem and the
想法是不允许他产生的客户认识您并产生任何
idea is that the client he's not allowed
to generate you know and generate any
输出主要的不允许产生任何输出以及我们
output the primary's not allowed to
generate any output and what we're
现在谈论的是此输出，直到备份确认它为止
talking about now is this output here
until the backup acknowledges that it
到目前为止已收到所有日志记录，因此
has received all log records up to this
point so the real sequence at the
主节点，然后让我们撤消崩溃主节点从10开始返回
primary then let's now undone crash the
primary go back to them starting at 10
现在，当输出规则是输入到达
the real sequence now when the output
rule is that the input arrives at the
输入到达的时间，即虚拟机监视器发送的副本
time the input arrives that's when the
virtual machine monitor sends a copy of
备份的输入，因此此日志消息的时间类型
the input to the backup so the the sort
of time at which this log message with
输入的发送要严格在主服务器生成输出之前
the input is sent is before strictly
before the primary generates the output
在通过网络触发此日志条目后，现在很明显
sort of obvious then after firing this
log entry off across a network and now
它正在走向备份，但我已经迷路了，不是虚拟的
it's heading towards the backup but I'd
have been lost my not the virtual
机器监视器向其生成的主服务器软件发送请求
machine monitor delivers a request to
the primary server software it generates
现在的输出
the output so now the
复制您知道主要对象实际上已生成更改状态211
replicated you know the primary has
actually generated change the state 211
并生成一个输出数据包，其中显示了11个，但虚拟机监视器
and generated an output packet that says
eleven but the virtual machine monitor
说哦，等等，我们不允许生成该输出，直到所有
says oh wait a minute we're not allowed
to generate that output until all
备份已确认先前的日志记录，因此您知道
previous log records have been
acknowledged by the backup so you know
这是最近的前一个日志消息，因此此输出由
this is the most recent previous log
message so this output is held by the
虚拟机监视，直到此日志条目包含输入数据包为止
virtual machine monitor until the this
log entry containing the input packet
从客户端传送到虚拟机监视器并由
from the client is delivered to the
virtual machine monitor and buffered by
虚拟机监视器，但不一定执行它，可能只是
the virtual machine monitor but do not
necessarily execute it it may be just
等待备份到达指令流中的那个点，然后
waiting for the backup to get to that
point in the instruction stream and then
虚拟机监视器将在此处发送活动数据包，说是的，我
the virtual machine monitor here will
send an active packet back saying yes I
确实获得了该输入，并且只有当确认返回时，才会
did get that input and when the
acknowledgment comes back only then will
虚拟机监视器在此处将数据包释放到网络上，因此
the virtual machine monitor here release
the packet out onto the network and so
这个想法是，如果客户本可以看到答复，那么必然
the idea is that if the client could
have seen the reply then necessarily the
备份必须已经看到了请求并至少将其缓冲了，因此我们不再
backup must have seen the request and at
least buffered it and so we no longer
在这种奇怪的情况下，客户可以看到答复，但随后
get this weird situation in which a
client can see a reply but then there's
故障和切入，副本对以下信息一无所知
a failure and a cut over and the replica
didn't know anything about that reply if
您知道还有一种情况，也许这条消息丢失了，如果这
the you know there's also a situation
maybe this message was lost and if this
日志条目丢失，然后主数据库崩溃了，因为它没有
log entry was lost and then the primary
crashes well since it hadn't been
已交付，因此备份没有发送操作，这意味着如果主服务器崩溃了
delivered so the backup hadn't sent the
act that means if the primary crashed
您知道此日志条目是在主要崩溃中带来的，它肯定已经崩溃了
you know this log entry was brought in
the primary crashed it must have crashed
在虚拟机监控器之前或至少在输出数据包和祈祷之前
before the virtual machine monitor or at
least the output packet and prayer for
该客户无法得到答复，因此无法
this client couldn't have gotten the
reply and so it's not in a position to
找出他们已经对输出规则满意的任何违规行为
spot any irregularities they're already
happy with the output rule
brennon看到我不知道他们不写论文没有提到虚拟
brennon see I don't know they don't
paper doesn't mention how the virtual
实现了机器监视器，我的意思是这是非常低级的东西，因为您
machine monitor is implemented I mean
it's pretty low level stuff because you
知道它坐在那里分配内存并计算页表，
know it's sitting there allocating
memory and figuring page tables and
与设备驱动程序交谈并拦截指令
talking to device drivers and
intercepting instructions and
了解客人正在执行什么指令，所以我们在说
understanding what instructions the
guest was executing so we're talking
关于低级的东西，您通常使用哪种语言写成C或
about low-level stuff what language is
written in you know traditionally C or
C ++，但我实际上不知道好吗，主要的延迟了
C++ but I don't actually know okay this
of the primary has to delay at this
等待备份说它是最新的，这是真实的
point waiting for the backup to say that
it's up to date this is a real
几乎每种复制方案都存在性能问题
performance thorn in the side of just
about every replication scheme this sort
同步等待的时间，我们不能让主对象超前
of synchronous wait where the we can't
let the primary get too far ahead of the
进行备份，因为如果主数据库在发生故障时发生故障，那将是
backup because if the primary failed
while it was ahead that would be the
备份滞后于客户端，因此几乎每个复制都滞后
backup lagging lagging behind clients
right so just about every replication
系统有这个问题，在某个时候主节点必须停滞等待
system has this problem that at some
point the primary has to stall waiting
进行备份，即使计算机是
for the backup and it's a real limit on
performance even if the machines are
像并排和相邻的架子，仍然是您知道我们在谈论
like side-by-side and adjacent racks
it's still you know we're talking about
一个半毫秒左右的时间来发送消息
a half a millisecond or something to
send messages back and forth with a
主要停滞了，如果我们想承受地震或全市范围内的电力
primary stalled and if we wanna like
withstand earthquakes or citywide power
您知道备份中的主要故障必须位于不同的城市
failures you know the primary in the
backup have to be in different cities
如果我们每次产生输出，那大概相隔五毫秒
that's probably five milliseconds apart
every time we produce output if we
将每个数据包复制到不同城市的两个副本中
replicate in the two replicas in
different city every packet that it
产生此输出必须首先等待五毫秒或其他
produces this output has to first wait
the five milliseconds or whatever to
有最后一个日志条目进入备份，以及他们如何需要Osment
have the last log entry get to the
backup and how they need Osment come
返回，然后我们可以释放路径包，您知道有点低
back and then we can release a path
packet and you know for sort of low
强度服务不是问题，但如果我们要建立一个
intensity services that's not a problem
but if we're building a you know
我们希望您知道的数据库服务器不是
database server that we would like to
you know that if it weren't for this
每秒可以处理数百万个请求
could process millions of requests per
second then
这真是令人难以置信的性能损失，这是为什么
that's just unbelievably damaging for
performance and this is a big reason why
您认识的人您知道他们是否可以使用复制方案
people you know you know if they
possibly can use a replication scheme
在更高层次上运作，并且有点理解
that's operating at a higher level and
kind of understands the semantics of
操作，因此它不必在您知道可以的每个数据包上停顿
operations and so it doesn't have to
stall on every packet you know it could
在每个高级操作上都停滞不前，甚至注意到您知道只读
stall on every high level operation or
even notice that well you know read-only
操作并不一定要停顿，仅此而已
operations don't have to stall at all
it's only right so that just all or
某些东西，但是你必须要有一个应用程序级的复制
something but you have to there has to
be an application level replication
实现您绝对正确的方案，因此观察是
scheme to to realize that you're
absolutely right so the observation is
您不必暂停仅拥有的主程序的执行
that you don't have to stall the
execution of the primary you only have
保持输出，所以也许这还不算很糟糕，但是
to hold the output and so maybe that's
not as bad as it could be but
但是，这意味着您在服务中认识的每个人都可以
nevertheless it means that every you
know in a service that could otherwise
在几微秒内对您知道的客户端做出了响应
have responded in a couple of
microseconds to the client you know if
我们必须先更新下一个城市中的副本，我们去了解一下10
we have to first update the replicas in
the next city we turn to you know 10
微秒互动，如果您有10毫秒互动，
micro second interaction into it 10
millisecond interactions possibly if you
有大量的客户提交并发请求，那么您可能
have vast numbers of clients submitting
concurrent requests then you may may be
即使在高延迟下也能够保持高吞吐量，但是您必须
able to maintain high throughput even
with high latency but you have to be
幸运或非常聪明的设计师能够做到这一点
lucky to or very clever designer to get
that
这是一个好主意，但是如果您登录主数据库的内存，该日志将
that's a great idea but if you log in
the memory of the primary that log will
当主要崩溃或服务器的通常语义消失时
disappear when the primary crashes or
that's usual semantics of a server
失败的是，您失去了包装盒内的所有物品，例如
failing is that you lose everything
inside the box like the contents of
记忆，或者即使失败，您也知道是否有人失败
memory or you know if even if you didn't
if the failure is that somebody
即使从电源插座上意外拔出电源线
unplugged the power cable accidentally
from the primary even if the primary
只是有电池备份的RAM或我不知道你不能得到什么
just has battery backed up RAM or I
don't know what you can't get at it
好吧，备份无法实现，因此实际上该系统确实记录了输出
all right the backup can't get at it so
in fact this system does log the output
它记录的位置在备份的内存中，以便
and the place it logs it is in the
memory of the backup and in order to
可靠地将其记录在那里，您必须遵守输出规则并等待
reliably log it there you have to
observe the output rule and wait for the
确认，所以这是完全正确的想法，只是不能使用主数据库的内存
acknowledgment so it's entirely correct
idea just can't use the primary's memory
为此，是的
for it yes
再说一遍，这是一个聪明的主意，所以问题可能是输入
say it again that's a clever idea I'd
and so the question is maybe input
应该去主要的，但是输出应该来自备份
should go to the primary but output
should come from the backup
我完全没有想到这一点可能会起作用
I completely haven't thought this
through that might work that
我不知道那很有趣
I don't know that's interesting
是的，也许我会
yeah maybe I will
好吧，这确实暴露出的一种可能性是，您知道的情况
okay one possibility this does expose
though is that the situation you know
可能是主服务器在释放其输出后崩溃，因此客户端会
maybe the a primary crashes after its
output is released so the client does
收到答复，然后主数据库崩溃，备份输入仍在
receive the reply then the primary
crashes the backups input is still in
尚未备份的虚拟机监视器中的此事件缓冲区
this event buffer in the virtual machine
monitor of the backup it hasn't been
备份上线后交付给实际的复制服务
delivered to the actual replicated
service when the backup goes live after
主数据库崩溃时，备份首先必须消耗所有
the crash of the primary the backup
first has to consume all of the sort of
尚未使用X的日志记录，必须赶上X
log records that are lying around that
it hasn't consumed X it has to catch up
到主数据库，否则它将不会接管相同的状态，因此在
to the primary otherwise it won't take
over with the same state so before the
备份可以上线，实际上它必须消耗所有这些条目，最后一个条目
backup can go live it actually has to
consume all these entries the last entry
大概是客户端的请求，因此备份将在之后生效
is presumably is the request from the
client so the backup will be live after
在它之后，在从客户端传递请求的中断之后，
after it after the interrupt that
delivers the request from the client and
这意味着您知道的备份将其计数器增加到11，然后
that means that the backup well you know
increment its counter to eleven and then
生成一个输出数据包，由于它已经存在，它将生成
generate an output packet and since it's
live at this point it will generate the
输出数据包，客户端将得到十一个答复，如果
output packet and the client will get to
eleven replies which is also if it if
真正发生的事情可能是异常的，可能不是
that really happened would be anomalous
like possibly not something that could
如果只有一台服务器，那么好消息是几乎可以肯定地
几乎可以肯定，客户端正在使用TCP和
the almost certainly the client is
talking to this service using TCP and
这是请求和响应在TCP上来回传递
that this is the request and the
response go back and forth on a TCP
由于状态相同，引导备份何时接管备份
Channel the when the backup takes over
the backup since the state is identical
到主节点，它知道有关该TCP连接的所有信息，以及是否所有
to the primaries it knows all about that
TCP connection and whether all the
序列号是and whatnot，当它生成此数据包时，它将
sequence numbers are and whatnot and
when it generates this packet it will
使用与原始数据包和TCP相同的TCP序列号生成它
generate it with the same TCP sequence
number as an original packet and the TCP
客户端上的堆栈会说，哦，等等，这是重复的数据包
我们将在TCP级别和用户级别丢弃重复的数据包
we'll discard the duplicate packet at
the TCP level and the user level
软件将永远不会看到此重复项，因此该系统确实是您
software will just never see this
duplicate and so this system really you
知道您可以将其视为一种偶然或聪明的把戏，但事实
know you can view this as a kind of
accidental or clever trick but the fact
适用于可能发生转换的任何复制系统
is for any replication system where
cutover can happen which is to say
几乎所有复制系统都几乎不可能在其中设计它们
pretty much any replication system it's
essentially impossible to design them in
一种保证他们基本上不会产生重复输出的方式
知道你很好，你可以在任何一侧犯错，我什至都不产生
know you well you can err on either side
I'm not even either not generate the
输出会很糟糕，这很糟糕，或者您可能会生成
output at all which would be bad which
would be terrible or you can generate
基本上没有办法生成割接的输出两次
保证只产生一次，每个人都可能出错
guaranteed generated only once everybody
errors on the side of possibly
生成重复的输出，这意味着在某种程度上您知道
generating duplicate output and that
means that at some level you know the
所有复制方案的客户端都需要某种重复检测
client side of all replication schemes
need some sort of duplicate detection
我们在这里使用TCP方案，而我们没有TCP
scheme here we get to use TCP s that we
didn't have TCP that would have to be
其他的东西也许是应用程序级别的序列号，或者我不知道是什么
something else maybe application level
sequence numbers or I don't know what
您会看到所有这些，实际上您会看到本质上的版本
and you'll see all of this and actually
you'll see versions of essentially
我说过的所有内容，例如实验2和3中的输出规则
everything I've talked about like the
output rule for example in labs 2 & 3
您将设计自己的复制状态机是
you'll design your own replicated state
machine yes
对第一部分是“是”，因此方案是主要发送答复，然后
yes to the first part so the scenario is
the primary sends the reply and then
主要发送衣服包或客户端关闭连接
either the primary send the clothes
packet or the client closes the connect
TCP连接收到主服务器的答复后，所以现在好像没有
the TCP connection after it receives the
primary's reply so now there's like no
客户端上有连接，但备用端上有连接
connection on the client side but there
is a connection on the backup side and
因此现在进行备份，以便备份使用最后一个日志条目作为
so now the backup so the backup consumes
the very last log entry that as the
输入现已生效，因此我们不负责在
input is now live so we're not
responsible for replicating anything at
这是正确的，因为现在备份已经存在，没有其他副本了
this point right because the backup now
live there's no other replica as the
主节点死了，所以如果备份执行失败，我们就不这样做
primary died so there's no like if if we
don't if the backup fails to execute in
与主要对象的锁步实际上是正确的，因为主要对象已死
lockstep with the primary that's fine
actually because the primary is is dead
而且我们不想与它同步执行，所以入门是
and we do not want to execute in
lockstep with it okay so the primer is
现在不是实时的，它在此TCP连接上生成了一个未关闭的输出
now not it's live it generates an output
on this TCP connection that isn't closed
但是从备份的角度来看，此数据包与客户端一起到达CCP
yet from the backup point of view this
packet arrives with the client on a CCP
从客户端的角度来看，不再存在的连接不再
connection that doesn't exist anymore
from the clients point of view like no
客户对他的大呼声，他只是要扔掉小包
big whoopee on the client right he's
just going to throw away the packet as
如果什么都没发生，则应用程序无法执行，客户端可以发送重置消息
if nothing happened the application
won't no the client may send a reset
诸如TCP错误之类的内容或返回备份的任何数据包
something like a TCP error or whatever
packet back to the backup and the backup
用它做某事或其他，但是没关系，因为我们不是
does something or other with it but it
doesn't matter because we're not
远离任何事物，因为没有主要的事物可以
diverging from anything because there's
no primary to diverge from you can just
处理我们说过但喜欢的流浪，实际上它要做的基本上是
handle a stray we said however it likes
and what it'll in fact do is basically
忽略，但是现在没有备份已经上线了，只是没有，我们不欠
ignore but there's no now the backup has
gone live there's just no we don't owe
任何人只要复制是的
anybody anything as far as replication
yeah
好吧，您可以打赌，因为备份内存映像与
well you can bet since the backups
memory image is identical to the
主要映像表示他们正在使用相同的源TCP发送数据包
primaries image that they're sending
packets with the very same source TCP
数字，它们是非常相同的，它们发送的所有内容都一点一点相同
number and they're very same everything
they're sending bit for bit identical
您知道此级别的数据包服务器没有IP地址或
packets you know at this level the
server's don't have IP addresses or for
我们的目的是您知道备份虚拟机中主要的虚拟机
our purposes the virtual machines you
know the primary in the back up virtual
机器具有IP地址，但物理计算机和vmm是
machines have IP addresses but the the
physical computer and the vmm are
对网络透明这不是完全正确，但基本上是
transparent to the network it's not
entirely true but it's basically the
物理机中的虚拟机监视器确实没有的情况
case that the virtual machine monitor in
the physical machine don't really have
自己在网络上的身份，因为您可以配置该身份
identity of their own on the network
because you can configure that then that
方式相反，这些不是您知道缝纫的虚拟机
way instead these they're not you know
the virtual machine with a sewing
操作系统在其自己的TCP堆栈中，它下面没有IP地址
operating system in its own TCP stack it
doesn't IP address underneath there an
地址以及所有其他内容，这些内容在
address and all this other stuff which
is identical between the primary in the
备份，并在发送数据包时将其与虚拟机IP一起发送
backup and when it sends a packet it
sends it with the virtual machines IP
地址和以太网地址，以及我的思维模型中最少的那些位
address and Ethernet address and those
bits least in my mental model are just
只需传递到局域网，这正是我们想要的
simply passed through on to the local
area network it's exactly what we want
所以我认为他不会产生与
and so I think he doesn't generate
exactly the same packets that the
主要会产生一些骗术
primary would have generated there's
maybe a little bit of trickery
你知道我们如果将这些实际上插入以太网的情况
you know what the we if this is these
are actually plugged into an Ethernet
切换到物理机，也许不是在一个计算机的两个不同端口中
switch into the physical machines maybe
it wasn't in two different ports of an
以太网交换机，我们希望以太网交换机改变主意
Ethernet switch and we'd like the
Ethernet switch to change its mind about
这两个机器中的哪个传送带有复制的数据包
which of these two machines that
delivers packets with replicated
服务以太网地址，所以那里有一些有趣的事情
services Ethernet address and so there's
a little bit of funny business there for
大多数情况下，它们只是生成相同的数据包，所以让我发送
the most part they're just generating
identical packets so let me just send
他们出来
them out
好吧，我一直在讲的另一个小细节是我一直在假设
okay so another little detail I've been
glossing over is that I've been assuming
主数据库刚刚失败或备份刚刚失败即失败停止
that the primary just fails or the
backup just fails that is fail stop
是的，但这不是唯一的选择，另一个非常常见的情况是
right but that's not the only option
another very common situation that has
要处理的是，如果两台计算机仍处于启动状态并且正在运行并正在执行
to be dealt with is if the two machines
are still up and running and executing
但是网络上发生了一件有趣的事情，导致他们无法
but there's something funny happen on
the network that causes them not to be
能够互相交谈，但仍然能够与某些客户交谈，所以如果
able to talk to each other but to still
be able to talk to some clients so if
如果主备份无法互相通信，则会发生这种情况
that happened if the primary backup
couldn't talk to each other but they
仍然可以与客户交谈，他们都会认为哦，其他副本
could still talk to the clients they
would both think oh the other replicas
死了，我最好接管并上线，所以现在我们有两台机器上线
dead I better take over and go live and
so now we have two machines going live
有了这项服务，现在您知道他们不再互相发送日志
with this service and now you know
they're no longer sending each other log
事件或他们只是分歧的任何事情，也许他们正在接受
events or anything they're just
diverging maybe they're accepting
不同的客户输入和更改以不同的方式停留，所以现在我们有了
different client inputs and changes are
stayed in different ways so now we have
如果我们让备份中的主节点上线，那将是一场裂脑灾难
a split brain disaster if we let the
primary in the backup go live because it
是一个发生故障的网络，而不是这些机器，
was a network that has some kind of
failure instead of these machines and
我的意思是本文解决之道是通过寻求外部权威
the way that this paper solves it I mean
is by appealing to an outside authority
做出关于允许使用哪个主要备份的决定
to make the decision about which of the
primary of the backup is allowed to be
活着，所以他们就是您，您知道事实证明他们的存储空间实际上不是
live and so it they're you know it turns
out that their storage is actually not
在本地磁盘上这几乎没有关系，但是它们的存储在某些外部
on local disk this almost doesn't matter
but their storage is on some external
磁盘服务器以及完全独立于该服务器中
disk server and as well as being in this
server as a like totally separate
服务与磁盘无关，该服务器恰好中止了该操作
service there's nothing to do with disks
there this server happens to abort this
通过网络进行测试并设置测试并设置服务，您可以在其中发送
test and set test and set service over
the network where you you can send a
测试并为其设置请求，并在内存中保留一些标志，
test and set request to it and there's
some flag it's keeping in memory and
它将设置标志并返回原来的值，因此主要值和备用值
it'll set the flag and return what the
old value was so both primary and backup
必须获得此测试并设置标志，有点像锁
have to sort of acquire this test and
set flag it's a little bit like a lock
为了上线，他们都可以在同一时间发送测试和设置请求
in order to go live they both may be
send test and set requests at the same
是时候进行此测试并设置服务器了，第一个得到答复，说哦
time to this test and set server the
first one gets back a reply that says oh
该标志曾经是零，现在是一个
the flag used to be zero now it's one
this
从测试集服务器获得响应的第二个请求是哦
second request to arrive the response
from the testing set server is Oh
实际上，当您的请求到达时，标志已经是一个
actually the flag was already one when
your request arrived so so basically
您不允许成为主要用户，因此，此测试和设置服务器可以
you're not allowed to be primary and so
this this test and set server and we can
认为它是一台机器，是由仲裁员决定两者中的哪一个
think of it as a single machine is the
arbitrator that decides which of the two
如果他们俩都认为其他人因网络而死亡，则应该上线
should go live if they both think the
other ones dead due to a network
对有关此机制的所有问题进行分区，如果测试失败，是的
partition any questions about this
mechanism you're busted yeah if the test
并且设置服务器应该在关键时刻关闭，而实际上
and set server should be dead at the
critical moment when and so actually
即使在所有情况下都没有网络分区，
even if there's not a network partition
under all circumstances in which one or
其中一个想要上线，因为它认为其他人甚至死了
the other of these wants to go live
because it thinks the others dead even
当另一个真的死了时，想要碰撞的那个仍然必须
when the other one really is dead the
one that wants to collide still has to
获取测试并设置锁定，因为类似于6:18的深层规则之一
acquire the test and set lock because
one of like the deep rules of 6:18 for
游戏是您无法分辨是否有另一台计算机坏掉了
game is that you cannot tell whether or
another computer is dead or not all you
知道是您停止从中接收数据包，并且您不知道
know is that you stopped receiving
packets from it and you don't know
是因为另一台计算机坏掉还是因为某事已消失
whether it's because the other computer
is dead or because something has gone
您和另一台计算机之间的网络有问题，因此所有备份
wrong with the network between you and
the other computer so all the backup
停得很好，我被卡在包中了，也许主要的已经死了，也许还活着
ceases well I've stuck in packets maybe
the primary is dead maybe it's live
主要对象可能会看到相同的内容，因此，如果存在网络分区，它们
primary probably sees the same thing so
if there's a network partition they
自该服务器以来，肯定不得不询问TAT，但由于他们不知道是否
certainly have to ask the TAT since that
server but since they don't know if it's
一个网络分区，他们必须询问测试集服务器，而不管是否
a network partition they have to ask the
testing set server regardless of whether
它是不是一个分区，所以无论何时想要碰撞测试并进行设置
it's a partition or not so anytime
either wants to collide the test and set
服务器还必须处于活动状态，因为他们始终必须获取此测试集
server also has to be alive because they
always have to acquire this testing set
锁定，因此测试和设置服务器听起来像是单点故障
lock so the test and set server
sounds like a single point of failure
他们试图建立一个复制的容错机制，除了
they were trying to build a replicated
fault tolerant whatever thing but in the
结束，您知道我们将无法进行故障转移，除非它仍然有效，所以这有点
end you know we can't failover unless
unless this is alive so that's a bit of
我正在猜测一个笨蛋，尽管我正在变得强大
a bummer
I'm guessing though I'm making a strong
猜测测试和设置服务器本身实际上是一个复制服务，并且
guess that the test and set server is
actually itself a replicated service and
是容错的权利，几乎可以肯定，我的意思是这些人正在
is fault tolerant right it's almost
certainly I mean these people are being
他们很高兴向您出售百万美元的高可用性存储
where they're like happy to sell you a
million dollar highly available storage
使用大量复制的系统
system that
uses enormous amounts of replication
内部um，因为测试设置在服务器上，我是
internally um since the testing set
thing is on there dis server I'm I'm
猜猜它也被复制了，您将在实验2和实验3中做的工作
guessing it's replicated too and the
stuff you'll be doing in lab 2 in lab 3
足以让您构建自己的容错测试，并且
is more than powerful enough for you to
build your own fault-tolerant test and
设置服务器，以便可以轻松解决此问题
set server so this problem can easily be
eliminated